<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>Humanists of Miami</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io/"/>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io/</id>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 25 August 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/08/24/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 25 August 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/08/24/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 25 August 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;PROLOGUE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Regarding the title of his famous novel, Il nomme della rosa, author Umberto Eco said he preferred a title with the least information possible. In the style of Charlotte Brontë’s Jane Eyre, or Arthur Conan Doyle’s Sherlock Holmes, it was Eco’s hope to name the novel “Adso da Melk,” after its protagonist. In the same style, I’d prefer to title these entries only after the dates on which they were written. Unfortunately, Eco was pressured by his publisher to rename his novel (in English: The Name of the Rose) as titles after the protagonist were unpopular in the Italian industry. In the same style, I’m forced to properly name these entries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Our first meeting of the semester is in the days prior to Mega Fair, and turns up most of its usual actors:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;
DRAMATIS PERSONAE&lt;br/&gt;
Nishan Amgain (Club President): A Senior of Physics&lt;br/&gt;
Aisulu “Ais” Murzagulova (Vice President): A Senior of Quantitative Economics&lt;br/&gt;
Connor Owens (Social Media Chair/PR): A Senior of Computer Science&lt;br/&gt;
Catarina Palmer (Myself; the Secretary): A Sophomore of Biochemistry&lt;br/&gt;
Evan Burke (Treasurer): A Sophomore of Biology and Neuroscience&lt;br/&gt;
Emil Sayahi (IT): A Sophomore of Computer Science&lt;br/&gt;
Grant McCrary (Events Coordinator): A Sophomore of Political Science&lt;br/&gt;
Ariana Noas (Just Here to Hang Out): A Junior of Social Work
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  By the time I completed this list, it was 8:50PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  We did manage to discuss, at relative length, intentions to expand club activities over the coming semesters. As nearly all of our membership intends to graduate this year, the accruement of new members is a must. Our plans are to coordinate with other clubs, particularly religious and cultural organizations on campus. Emil is compared to a video game character; Ais attempts to teach me the pronunciation of her surname. Nishan, finally, addresses the topics we intend to discuss this semester. No conclusions were reached, though many were broached.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 8 September 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/09/07/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 8 September 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/09/07/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 8 September 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;Philosophy of Language&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  There exists a question as to what constitutes a “language.” Certainly some “languages” are obvious– this text is written in a language, and the discussion it describes was spoken in a language. This raises problems of medium– is language not restricted to speech or text?– of origin– are synthetic languages, “conlangs,” languages in the same sense as natural languages?– and of recipient– what might we call code, the language of computers? One may argue, from these examples, that a “language” is something constituted of “words” that communicate “meaning.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Regardless of a language’s medium, origin, or recipient, the problem of meaning is constant. The philosophy of language is largely concerned with the communication of meaning, in particular, the explanation of what exists. Readers of philosophical texts will understand why this poses such an issue– even “approachable” philosophical texts will pose difficulty in their comprehension, by virtue of attempting to explain a concept so complex and abstract. This forces either the adoption of fiction (to quote Ursula K. Le Guin, “All fiction is metaphor… a metaphor for what? If I could have said it non-metaphorically, I would not have written all these words…”) or the creation of extremely dense non-fiction texts. The former may be more fun to read, but is more prone to misunderstanding, or even the erasure of meaning entirely. The latter is very often a chore: a textbook, consisting not of bland, factual statements (“the dipole moment describes the asymmetrical movement of electrons across a molecule…”) but instead sentences that are stupendous, insane, and false.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  The density and complexity of these texts spark debate as to the usefulness of language and language in its current state. Some argue about the “inaccessibility” of jargon– they claim that meaning could be more easily communicated in more simple, less specialized language. By these arguments, the onus for comprehension lies in the author’s word choice, their preference for words with more or fewer syllables, the latter choice always better, the former the tool only of masturbatory elites. There is some evidence of this– Latin, in many ways a “timeless” language, lost much of its complexity as Europe aged beyond the Roman empire. Regional dialects became “vulgar,” simplifying verbs and nouns as its speakers forgot or simply ceased to care about the minutiae (pronounced min-oo-ti-eye) of the language. Almost no modern Romance language retained all ten noun cases– forgotten were the four infinitives– no longer do we see the second person-plural-pluperfect-passive-subjunctive conjugation in Spanish or Italian or French. People simply do not retain language with rules that seem arcane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Yet how do we communicate meaning without jargon? How is the chemist to explain their field if, rather than use the word “electronegativity,” they must say explicitly “the tendency for an atom to attract electrons?” How should the small business manager explain his success to his investors if, rather than saying “profit,” he need state “the difference between the money spent creating and vending products and the money given in exchange for the product sold?” How might the linguist describe the language she studies if, rather than “verb,” she must say “the part of a lingual idea which describes an action, as opposed to an object or actor?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  We return to the question of how meaning is communicated, when language, as demonstrated, is so inherently flawed. Ludwig Wittgenstein argues in his Tractatus Logico-Philosophicus that the world consists not of objects, but facts (objects consisting not of matter, but logical arguments). To take this abstractly, that at least the way in which we interact with the world is dependent on our understanding of true and false clauses, one must ask how truth is communicated, and, from there, how one can understand a statement as true. From these questions we reveal that words carry no inherent meaning– if I say “the sky is blue,” but your understanding of “sky” is my understanding of “ground,” then my statement is, to you, false, and truth improperly communicated. This state of affairs– one we encounter every time we argue with a friend, or a teacher, or our parents, every time we try to articulate the gravity of an externally mundane experience– is tremendously lonely. We cannot escape language, even though, as Wittgenstein claimed, “whereof one cannot speak, thereof one must be silent.”&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 15 September 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/09/14/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 15 September 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/09/14/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 15 September 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;Separation of Art and Artist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  The “separation of art and artist” is an academic concept that has been debated for decades and, arguably, longer. Consider, for example, the preservation of ancient texts by scholars such as Aristotle, work which was for centuries done in an almost exclusively religious context. The monks tasked with transcribing the works of the Great Philosopher would have acknowledged him as a pagan or, worse, an atheist– yet he was known as the Great Philosopher nonetheless. In more modern history, famous playwright Oscar Wilde was arrested on charges of homosexuality, yet maintained massive popularity well into the contemporary era.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Yet it was not until the 20th century that critics began to move away from traditional literary criticism, which emphasized historical context and authorial circumstances in interpretation, to “death of the author,” which posited that literature (and, later, other forms of art) should be interpreted only from its end point: the final consumer decides the meaning of a work, regardless of authorial intention. The relationship between art and artist which had been historically almost unquestioned grew increasingly distal in the eyes of critics. Death of the author saw increasing popularity as academia grew more critical of the underrepresentation of authors of color and women authors within the Western canon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  With the advent of social media, authors have become increasingly visible in the public eye. No longer are viewers restricted in their understanding by the 24-hour news cycle– they may discover a creator’s thoughts, words, and misdeeds in real time. Not only this, but they may take matters of criticism into their own hands, not needing to wait for the weeks or months it may take to publish an editorial or mail a letter, but message a creator directly through websites such as Twitter and Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  As the public grows increasingly cognizant of an artist’s indiscretions, some have asked the morality in engaging with art by those unfavored within the public eye. Still others have argued for the separation of art and artist– that art may be engaged without considering, or even actively rejecting, its creator’s influence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  One must distinguish between interpretation and enjoyment, though both are equally related to the issue of art and artist: interpretation refers to one’s understanding of a work, what is gleaned, its message and meaning, while enjoyment refers simply to the pleasures a work of art may evoke. Should an artist’s questionable words or actions sour either? Some argue that, as learning new information about an author changes nothing intrinsically about their existing work, only enjoyment– which is purely intrinsic to the reader– will diminish when an author is found “problematic.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  However, not all subscribe to the author’s critical death– to many, art and artist are considered inseparable. The traditional theory of literary criticism remains popular. Art is, in many ways, a reflection of its artist. What thoughts, emotions, and actions had occurred within and around the artist exist also in their work. Take, for example, the work of H.P. Lovecraft, a phenomenal racist. His work centers around a fear of the strange of the unknown and, even within his work, is often closely linked with a fear of people of color– for example, by characterizing Native peoples as worshiping or abetting the eldritch gods. Despite the wild popularity of Lovecraft’s stories, his hatred of people of color is indivisible from the themes of his work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  One may also argue that, for as much as an artist’s emotions may affect their work, many creators avoid or even contradict their actions outside of their art. John Lennon of Beatles fame was a wifebeater and child abuser, yet his song Imagine was performed by celebrities such as Gal Godot as recently as the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic in a call for unity and kindness, and even by Lennon’s son after Russia’s 2022 invasion of Ukraine. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  With this in mind, one must consider the circumstances created by the entertainment industry and how many creators experience abuse throughout their careers. Should one have sympathy for the interpersonal conflicts of creators and celebrities, considering what abuses they may have faced, and how they experience constant scrutiny within the public eye?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Here we reach into the issue of consumption under capitalism: with the entertainment industry so corrupt, and so much art controlled by corporations such as Disney and Netflix, how much responsibility do individuals retain in the creation of and engagement with art? Does morality of consumption start and end with the material benefit wrought by faulty parties as this consumption occurs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  The issue of morality within creative consumption is a topic of debate perhaps as old as the written language, as works criticizing politically powerful entities have been constantly under fire. Whether art may be separated from its creator is intrinsic to this understanding of morality as, consistently, the desire to distinguish the two comes from an impression of moral conflict. On this subject matter, one may consider the opinions expressed by Oscar Wilde as he was attacked for homosexual themes in his work: to judge art not by its beauty, but by its moral merits, is a form of criticism for “brutes and illiterates.”&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 22 September 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/09/21/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 22 September 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/09/21/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 22 September 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;Who Deserves to be Flooded?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  The question is interpreted very literally. For the literal interpretation: Florida, Russia, Great Britain. Flooding in Pakistan, hurricanes in Puerto Rico. First world nations (esp. The US) largely responsible for conditions killing great numbers in developing countries– both through contributions to climate change (Pakistan) and through abuses under imperialistic rule (PR). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Climate accelerationism met with strong objections and nervous laughter. Colonial history in Pakistan and how developing countries suffer for 70-year-old emissions from the Global North– China’s emissions are the result of its ravaging by the West and subsequent rapid industrialization. Middle Eastern countries have the greatest emissions per capita. The economic value of oil– how it’s destroyed the Middle East and saved the Nords. Nationalization in Europe and Latin America. Ozone depletion and recovery over three decades. Exxon Mobile– formally the world’s largest company, but growing increasingly less powerful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  “Not to sound like a fucking Liberal, but if you watch John Oliver–” ‘carbon offsets’ largely snake oils. Tesla and its contributions to alternative energy– can state subsidized environmental protections have any effect? Technology needed for alternative energy manufacture also extremely environmentally taxing– back to Venezuela, lithium needed for electric car batteries largely mined in Latin America. Yet electric cars may still be better for the environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Many countries need oil and other environmentally taxing measures to maintain their economies, especially in the developing world. Should developed countries “claim” important environmental resources (e.g. the Amazon) in developing countries to protect it? Shareholders don’t care about climate change! “Green capitalism” is ultimately non-functional. Is capitalism the source, or the electoral system? Multi-partisan, or no parties (George Washington!)?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 29 September 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/09/28/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 29 September 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/09/28/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 29 September 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The limits of knowledge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Empiricism and its limits– the philosophy and David Hume and how, though science may be able to provide more certainty to an idea, it does not guarantee it. Pursuit of truth/knowledge as human nature and the distinction between knowledge as human nature and knowledge as a tool for human nature. Objective truth as fallacious. Structures of knowledge as relating to philosophy of mind– “knowing animal.” Knowledge:survival as parallel to to debates of altruism. Internal knowledge of identity as distinct from universal knowledge.&lt;br/&gt;
Knowledge is relative. “I know my address,” in the sense that when asked for my address, I may give an answer. But when asked for the nature of the universe, this knowledge is so far beyond a relevant, relative sphere that it cannot be comprehended, must less “known.” Semantic knowledge– Kant, “all bachelors are unmarried,” not because the speaker has met every bachelor, but because bachelors are by definition unmarried. Words must have meaning– convey “knowledge”– for any progress or prepositions, any science to move forward. In this sense things are “true,” by virtue of their meanings. Cannot “truth” be created through the creation of words (e.g. “all blombos are flingies”)? Unless truth is maintained by collective agreement.&lt;br/&gt;
Does any communication require the existence of axioms? “Definitions,” which may act as axioms, still vary when put down. Words change definitions over time– “meaning” is ephemeral. Meaning cannot even be communicated between individuals, regardless of to what extent they share experience, or how well “understood” the language used may be. Individuals are often unable to even communicate knowledge to themselves. Does knowledge exist if it cannot be communicated? Is anything conceivable, “knowable?” Does there exist anything “unknowable,” or “knowable?”&lt;br/&gt;
Nothing can be known for certain, but things may be known with very high probability. Humans do not act rationally! Do humans actually operate on any rational basis at all? Is there meaning in assigning meaning or reason to anything? The “real is rational.” Hegel. False argument that evolution “acts with intent.”&lt;br/&gt;
What is rationality? Following logical steps– either in self interest, or ethical interest. Rationality may be linked to achieving a specific goal– to behave efficiently. “Rationality” in fact implies intent to natural processes– evolution is not “rational,” because it does not have intent. Rationality as distinct from logic. Rationality may be based on logic– but is logic inherent? Is logic non-relative knowledge? That was the first question of the meeting!&lt;br/&gt;
“All of philosophy is wrong and you are right,” Schröedinger was a dumbass.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 13 October 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/10/12/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 13 October 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/10/12/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 13 October 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;Philosophy of Education&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My birthday is tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public education is a vehicle of indoctrination, but there is no alternative– children must be socialized. What kind of socialization should we value? Is it good that the public education system so strictly encourages rule following etc.? Modern school systems are much more lenient than historical schools. Education has always served as a form of indoctrination, but over the years the US has transitioned from marriage to any particular ideology or philosophy to a postmodern “anti-philosophy.” Education might be phrased as providing “cultural tools” as opposed to specific ideologies.&lt;br/&gt;
Should education be more vocational? Should children be compelled to attend school?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 20 October 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/10/19/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 20 October 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/10/19/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 20 October 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;Ship of Theseus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ship of Theseus as related to identity. Is identity directly continuous to identity? Identity exists “independently” of the body, but is still reliant on it. The Ship of Theseus may be said to be the same ship, not for its composition, but for its value to the people that used it and knew it. Douglas Adams’s experience with the Shinto shrine. Is identity contingent on the people with whom you interact? Who you are with your mom vs with your friends vs with your teachers etc. Tree falling in a forest etc. 2022 Physics Nobel prize as counter to theories of butterfly effect. Star Trek transporters. Buddhist conceptions of the self as a sophism.&lt;br/&gt;
Does the self expand with age? Can aspects of the self be “lost?” When a person is lost, one loses the identity they had in their presence. Do you wish you could be someone else? Does there exist a true, singular self? Not the same as being disingenuous– just that our self concept is dependent on interactions with others. Can identity be defined?– by demographic factors? Identity is always subject to change and dependent on environment. Might there be a “core” in identity?&lt;br/&gt;
Identity vs sense of self– morals, cognitive processes, etc distinct from identity and inarticulable. Identity may be defined through negatives, as a relative concept, while sense of self exists intrinsically. Is sense of self intrinsic, though? As even our understanding of our own cognitive processes occurs only relative to others, only with the understanding that there are others who are not like us. Does a sense of self still exist without a way to articulate it?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 3 November 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/11/02/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 3 November 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/11/02/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 3 November 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;Trolley Problem&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Do individuals have a responsibility to act when others commit (perceived) immoral acts? Can inaction that facilitates immoral acts be equivalized to those immoral acts? In theory, if individuals hold each other accountable, then immoral acts may be largely neutralized through individual actions. Can standard citizens then be held accountable for the actions of their government? Can powerful individuals be held accountable for the actions of their government? Can powerful governments be held accountable for the actions of other governments?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Perhaps, but the this idea has been used to justify historical acts of imperialism. Consider the draft, consider the value of the vote in the US and other countries. Not to conflate the complexity of ethics with a call to inaction. Cold War justifications, Middle East justifications. Is there an altruistic reason to intervene abroad? Russia-Ukraine war. Should the US be obligated to intervene in other conflicts before it is able to improve itself? But individuals are not our government– why are we obligated to think in the context of borders at all? Regardless of the ideological meaning of borders, or the material purpose of borders, and how well they fit within an ideal– borders exist. Resources are not unlimited– maximization is not always practical. National ties are ultimately family ties– would you sacrifice your family for the lives of strangers?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Catarina Palmer</name>
<email>palmer29@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 10 November 2022</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/11/09/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 10 November 2022/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2022/11/09/Secretary's Notes: Thursday, 10 November 2022/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;Ethics of Voting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Elections in 2 meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  There is a bit of a disconnect between Nishan’s attempts at appealing to both sides of the political spectrum and the actual political composition of the club: that is to say that we are just about all socialists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Should only “intelligent” (i.e. educated) people be allowed to vote? In which case, how is intelligence to be determined, and how is “intelligence” to be distinguished in context? How often does public opinion (established through votes) concur with an “advantageous” position? Is the way states are represented in the Senate and House of Representatives fair? What is the function of the Senate when its modern function has been primarily to inhibit the acts of the House? Why should States be represented in federal matters, as opposed to simply reflecting the judgment of the nation as a whole?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Why might someone not vote? Not everyone feels that party alignments are valuable, or that they are sufficiently educated to meaningfully vote. Is a vote even an action with moral characteristic? Would a multi-party or no-party system improve individual voice in US policy? Party and individual power becomes watered down once politicians enter the legislative floor. A multi party system often results in one party forming a majority anyway– how effective can a multi party be?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  What about the ethics of mandatory voting?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
<entry>
<author>
<name>Emil Sayahi</name>
<email>sayahie@miamioh.edu</email>
</author>
<title>Memo from the VP: Organisation Monthly Check-Ins</title>
<link href="https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2023/02/08/Memo from the VP: Organisation Monthly Check-Ins/"/>
<pubdate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubdate>
<updated>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</updated>
<id>https://humanists-of-miami.github.io//posts/2023/02/08/Memo from the VP: Organisation Monthly Check-Ins/</id>
<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Office of Student Activities is launching a pilot program this semester to build connections between similar student organisations and Student Activities staff.&lt;br/&gt;
These meetings will be held in McGuffey Hall 322, with &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1dp1fnIav1zB6AnK7B6XROgdI7SS6uxW5GuAqXrEMYkA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;a different meeting date for each category of organisation&lt;/a&gt; (note: each meeting is on a Friday). Any member of Humanists of Miami can attend. In addition to having members of other organisations in attendance, there will be a member of SEAL staff, and a SEAL Ambassador.&lt;br/&gt;
Humanists of Miami is considered both a ‘Political/Social Action’ and ‘Religious/Spiritual/Secular’ organisation, but this does not limit our members to only attending meetings for those two categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regards,&lt;br/&gt;
Emil&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>
</feed>